doctemplates.net 2018-01-21

# Privacy Policies of Document Templates

This Privacy Policy outlines the rights, services, and use of our website.

 **How Our Site Collects Information**

We only collect information when new subscribers sign up or someone leaves a comment. We never ask for banking or personal information, we only use your email address.

 **Collected Information Use**

We only use your email address for keeping you updated on changes to the website. We like to keep our subscribers informed about the latest trends and news. When someone requests information, we send out feedback to their email address that goes into our files. Users may stop receiving our emails at any time simply by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe link’ located at the bottom of each of our emails.

 **Protecting Your Information**

Every email address received at our website will be stored into a secure database. This database is attached to a web update software program that has been password protected. That means nobody else can access it except our website administration.

 **Cookies**

Anytime our templates are accessed, or a ‘favorite’ link is made to the site, we use cookies to track them.

No 3rd parties will ever be able to access your personal information. We never trade information or use it for advertisements of promotions.

 **Google Adsense Advertisements**

There may be times when Google Adsense advertisements appear on our site. This is the result of Google’s own Dart cookies that enables them to display more targeted ads. If you would like to read Google’s – ‘Ads and Content Network Privacy Policy’ – you can find it at <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>[__](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

 **Accepting Our Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions**

Doc Templates reserves the right to change our policy at any time we find it necessary. We will announce the updates and changes immediately after they are made. They will be highlighted, that way nobody should miss them. Subscribers should check back regularly to see if anything has changed. It is the subscribers responsibility to watch for updates on our site.

Anyone using the Doc Templates website is in agreement with this privacy policy, and by subscribing you are approving of this privacy policy.

 **CONTACT US**

Anyone with questions or in need of assistance with understanding this privacy policy, should contact us immediately.
